Yes, so as I said, I want to get started with creating an image,
but beforehand, I would prefer to sign in to my Microsoft account.
And in order to sign into Microsoft Designer,
you need a Microsoft account, so it can either be an Outlook email,
or anything like that that you have used before, or we can even sign up.
So let's try that over here.
Let's say that I come to sign in, right?
I click on sign in, and I will be forwarded to logging.microsoftdownline.com.
So over here, it says sign in.
Or if no account, create one, right?
So let's click on create one to see what we can have over there.
Yes, so it says create your Microsoft account, enter your email address.
Let's say that I want to add up my Google email,
like I say, this is my email address at gmail.com.
And I click next to see what comes next.
It says you already have an account.
There is already a Microsoft account with the email address.
If it's yours, click on sign in.
So I do that.
And I wait a little bit.
Get a code to sign in.
We've sent a code.
OK.
So let me check my email right now,
and bring out the code for you guys.
So it says we're updating our terms, as you see.
I click next.
And what's next Microsoft?
Sign in faster with your face, finger print or pin.
So I skip for now.
And I just want to get to the Microsoft designer as soon as possible, right?
Stay signed in.
Yes, I want to stay signed in.
Thank you.
And as you see, I am back to designer.microsoft.com.
So again, I wait a little bit.
And as you see, over here, it's written NG,
Neemile Lassamy.
So this means that I am already signed in.